gilttaste.com 2018-06-17

# Privacy Notice | Gilt Groupe | About

_Last updated May 23, 2018_

Thank you for visiting our website for Gilt Groupe ("Gilt"), which is part of the Hudson's Bay Company family of company sites. We are committed to providing an exciting and safe online shopping experience and elevated level of personal service synonymous with Gilt. This commitment includes respecting and protecting the privacy of your personal information.

This privacy policy describes the types of information we collect from and about you when you visit our website (each a "Site"), use our mobile applications (each an "App"), visit or make a purchase at our stores (each a "Store"), or otherwise contact or interact with us offline ("Offline Services"). The Sites, Apps, Stores, and Offline Services are collectively referred to as the "Services." This privacy policy also explains how Gilt may use and share your personal information, as well as your ability to control certain uses of it.

By using the Services, you agree to the collection, use, and disclosure of your information as described in this privacy policy, and agree to the Terms of Use which are incorporated by reference. If you do not agree, please do not access or use the Services.

### **FREQUENTLY ASKED QUESTIONS**

What information does Gilt collect?   
What are my Tracking Options?   
How does Gilt use the information collected?   
What information does Gilt share with others?   
How can I view, update, or remove my information?   
What choices do I have about receiving communications from Gilt?   
What are my California Privacy Rights?   
What about children's privacy?   
What about security?   
What about other websites?   
For how long and where is my data stored?   
What if I live outside of the United States?   
How does Gilt communicate changes to this Policy?   
Whom do I contact if I have additional questions or concerns about this policy?

**Q: What information does Gilt collect?**

**A:** Gilt may collect information from or about you in a number of ways. **Please note that if you decline to provide any of the requested information (whether or not required), you may not be able to take full advantage of the Services and their features or make a purchase from us.**

From Gilt's Interactions With You: We collect information from and about you and your transactions and other interactions with us. This may include when you use the Services, create an online account with us, make a purchase, sign up for our catalogue, newsletters or email lists, participate in sweepstakes, contests or other promotions, participate in a product review, survey, or other similar programs, send a gift or virtual gift card to a person, or otherwise contact us. The personal information we collect may include your name, address, email address, telephone number, or other contact information, loyalty program membership information, gender, birthday, age, other demographic information, your interests, and preferences.

If you make a purchase from us, we may also collect a credit or debit card number or other financial information, CVV, and billing address. In addition, if you make a purchase at a designer boutique, restaurant, salon, or other similar service offered within a section of a Gilt store that is leased by a third party) (each a "Boutique Service"), we and the Boutique Service may collect information such as your name, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, email address and payment or gift card information, and their privacy policies govern their use of your information.

If you download one of our Apps, you may choose to permit the App to obtain your precise geolocation. In this case, we will determine your zip code from the precise location data received from your mobile device. We do not store precise location data; we only store the zip code associated with the location.

**Information You Provide About a Third Party:** If you send someone else a communication from the Services (such as sending a gift or virtual gift card), we may collect information such as that person's name, telephone number, email, and/or shipping address.

**Automatically on the Site or App:** We, or our service providers, may use cookies, web beacons/pixel tags, log files, and other technologies to collect certain non-personal information about visitors to our Site or App, users of our online services, and interactions with our emails and online advertisements, and to allow Gilt to keep track of analytics and certain statistical information. For example, we may collect information such as your browser type, operating system type or mobile device model, viewed webpages, links that are clicked, IP address, mobile device identifier or other unique identifier, sites or apps visited before coming to our Site or App, the amount of time you spend viewing or using the Site or App, the number of times you return, or other click-stream or site usage data, emails we send that you open, forward, or click through to our Site or App. Collecting this information, and linking it with your personal information, helps us to tailor our Site and App and enhance your online shopping experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular Site or App, and to help identify Site or App features, promotions, advertisements, and offers that may be of particular interest to you and retarget online and mobile advertisements to you across computers or devices you may use.

**From Third Party Sources:** We may acquire information from other sources to update or supplement the information that you provide or that we collect automatically (such as information to validate or update your address or other demographic information), or when you connect with the company through a third party (including through social networks) based on your registration and privacy settings on those third party sites.

**Combination of Information:** We may combine the information we receive from or about you, including information you provide to us and information we automatically collect through the Site or App, as well as information across other computers or devices that you use, with information we collect or receive about you from other online and offline sources, or from other third party sources.

**Third Party Analytics and Advertisements:** We also may use third party advertisements, analytics, and tracking tools to better understand who is using the Site or App, how people are using the Site or App, how to improve the effectiveness of the Services and related content, and to help us or those third parties serve more targeted advertising to you across the Internet. These third parties may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, flash cookies, or other technologies to collect and store non-personal information. They may also combine information they collect from your interaction with the Site or App with information they collect from other sources. We do not have access to, or control over, these third parties' use of cookies or other tracking technologies.

**Q: What are my Tracking Options?**

**A:** Certain parts of the Site and App require cookies. You can set your browser or operating system settings to limit certain tracking or to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site or App or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please refer to your Web browser's or operating system's website or "Help" section for more information on how to delete and/or disable your browser or operating system from receiving cookies or controlling your tracking preferences.

Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers. We may use cookies or other technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and to link data collected across other computers or devices that you may use. To understand your choices for receiving more relevant advertising or to manage your settings, please review the information below:

• To learn more about managing your privacy and storage settings and opting out from receiving third party advertiser cookies, you may visit the Network Advertising Initiative's opt-out page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.  
• If you wish to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, Google has developed the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.  
• On your mobile device, you may also adjust your privacy and advertising settings to control whether you want to receive more relevant advertising.

**Q: How does Gilt use the information collected?**

A: Gilt may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes:

• To validate, confirm, verify, deliver, install, and track your order (including to process payment card transactions, arrange for shipping, handle returns and refunds, maintain a record of the purchases you make, and contact you about your orders, including by telephone) or to service products you purchased from us.  
• To enhance your online shopping experience, including as a way to recognize you and welcome you to the Site or App.  
• To send you catalogs, information, newsletters, promotional materials and other offerings from Gilt or on behalf of our partners and affiliates.  
• To provide you with customized Site or App content, targeted offers, promotions and advertising on the Site or App, through other third party sites or apps, or via email, text messages, or App push notifications that are offered by Gilt or other marketing partners that might be of interest to you.  
• To improve our sites, products/services, customer service, and customer shopping experience.  
• To use your data in an aggregated non-specific format for analytical and demographic purposes.  
• To protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business, such as by protecting against and preventing fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims and other liabilities, and managing risk exposure, including by identifying potential hackers and other unauthorized users.  
• To contact you when necessary or requested, including responding to your questions and comments and providing customer support.  
• As otherwise described to you at the point of data collection. 

**Q: What information does Gilt share with others?**

**A:** Gilt will never sell or rent your personal information to third parties. Gilt may share personal information we collect from and about you in the following ways:

**Hudson's Bay Company Family:** We may share collected information within the Hudson's Bay Company family of affiliated companies (including Saks Fifth Avenue, Saks Fifth Avenue OFF 5TH, Hudson's Bay, Lord & Taylor, Gilt, Home Outfitters, and any future additions to the Hudson's Bay Company family of affiliated companies).

**Co-Marketing Partners:** Certain areas of the Services may be provided to you in association with third parties, such as companies that provide products and services, rewards programs, conduct joint sales programs (such as our Boutique Services in our stores), sweepstakes, promotional campaigns, and other jointly sponsored events. Such Services will identify the third party. If you elect to register for any products and/or services provided during the Services, you either will be providing your information to both Gilt and such third party, or Gilt might share your information directly with such third party for that third party to fulfill their products and our products and services directly with you.

**Other Third Parties:** Gilt may share your information with select partners, affiliates, and other third parties that we believe may have offers or be of interest to you.

**Legal Disclosures; Safety:** Gilt may transfer and/or disclose the information we receive from and about you to comply with a legal obligation; to provide information to law enforcement and other governmental authorities in accordance with applicable law, and when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. We also reserve the right to share information with legal authorities and other companies for fraud protection and credit risk reduction, to detect any technical or security vulnerabilities, to enforce our Terms of Use or other applicable policies, or to otherwise protect the rights, property, safety, or security of third parties, users of the Services, Gilt, or the public.

**Sale of Business:** During the normal course of our business, we may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires all or a part of a business within the Hudson's Bay Company family of affiliated companies, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against a business within the Hudson's Bay Company family of companies, such information may be considered an asset of the company and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personally identifiable information provided through the Services in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Service Providers:** We use third-party service providers to perform certain services on our behalf when the information is necessary for them to perform their duties. These third-party service providers are prohibited from using personal information for any other purpose and are contractually required to comply with all applicable laws and requirements, which may include Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards if they are processing payments for Gilt.

**Aggregate or Anonymous Non-Personal Information:** We may also share or sell non-identifiable aggregate or anonymous information with our affiliates, agents, service providers, business partners, or other third parties for their marketing or analytics uses or for other lawful purposes. This type of non-identifiable and aggregate information cannot be used to identify you personally.

**Q: How can I view, update or remove my information?**

**A:** If you have registered for an account or made a purchase, you may view and update your account information by logging into the "Your Account" section of the Site or App with your email address and password. Once logged in, you can view or update your name, address, telephone number or email address. You can also contact our Customer Service Department via email at [service@gilt.com](mailto:service@gilt.com) to access or update any of this information.

If you would like to remove or delete your profile or the personal information that Gilt has collected from or about you, please contact our Customer Service Department via email address at [service@gilt.com](mailto:service@gilt.com). We will process your request within a reasonable period of time. Any information that you previously posted may still be publicly viewable. Gilt may keep certain information and content in our backup files and archives.

**Residents of certain countries, including European Union member states (and the United Kingdom), may have additional rights listed under "What if I live outside of the United States?"**

**Q: What choices do I have about receiving communications from Gilt?**

**A:** To receive promotional offers from the Hudson's Bay Company family of affiliated companies, you can sign up on our Site or App or contact a Customer Service representative. If you register for an account or make a purchase, you will automatically receive promotional emails and direct mail from the Hudson's Bay Company family of affiliated companies. We provide our customers with the opportunity to "opt out" of having their information used for purposes not directly related to placement, processing, fulfillment or delivery of a product order. We provide you with the following options if you prefer to "opt out" of receiving information or materials that we think may be of interest to you:

**Electronic Promotional Offers:** At all times, you have the option of "opting out" of receiving promotional emails from the sender only by clicking the "unsubscribe" link in any of the promotional emails you receive. In addition, if you have an online account, you may change your email preferences regarding email from us by logging into the "Your Account" section of the Site or App.

**Direct Mail Promotional Offers:** If you would like to be removed from our Gilt catalog mailing list, please contact a Customer Service representative by email to stop receiving paper catalogs.

**Push Notifications:** When you use the App, you may receive push notifications. If you prefer not to receive push notifications, you may adjust your settings on your mobile device to control whether you want to receive these alerts.

**App Geolocation Information:** When you use the App on your mobile device, you may choose not to share your geolocation information with us by adjusting the device's location service settings.

**Other Contact:** In all cases, you may email us at [service@gilt.com](mailto:service@gilt.com) or [privacy@gilt.com](mailto:privacy@gilt.com).

If you receive marketing communications from one or more companies within the Hudson's Bay Company family of affiliated companies, you must opt-out individually from each of the companies from which you are receiving company-specific marketing communications.

**Q: What are my California Privacy Rights?**

**A:** If you are a California resident, you may request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties or affiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes. To make such request, please submit a written request to the following email address specifying that you want a copy of Gilt's "California Privacy Rights" notice: [privacy@gilt.com](mailto:privacy@gilt.com). Please include "Attn: California Privacy" in the subject line. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information. Please allow up to 30 days for us to process your request. You may submit such a request once per year.

Non-affiliated third parties are independent from Gilt and if you wish to receive information about your disclosure choices or stop communications from such third parties, you will need to contact those non-affiliated third parties directly.

**Q: What about children's privacy?**

**A:** Protecting children's privacy is important to us, and the Site and App are not intended for children under the age of thirteen. We do not direct the Site or App to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, such children. If Gilt learns that a child under the age of thirteen has provided personally identifiable information to the Site or App, it will use reasonable efforts to remove such information from its files.

**Q: What about security?**

**A:** We have taken certain physical, administrative, and technical steps to safeguard the information we collect from and about our customers and Site visitors. While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card information) on our forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

**Q: What about other websites?**

**A:** Our Site or App may include links to third-party websites or apps that are not affiliated with Gilt. These websites or apps may send their own cookies to visitors, collect data or solicit your information. The privacy policies of these other websites or apps may be very different from our policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites or apps and cannot guarantee the security of any personal information you provide to or collected by such third party sites or apps.

**Q: For how long and where is my data stored?**

**A:** Your personal information may be stored for as long as is reasonably necessary to perform the purposes listed under "How does Gilt use the information collected?" For example, if you create an online account with us, we will store any personal information associated with your account for as long as you maintain that account. If you make a purchase, we will store any personal information associated with that purchase to fulfill the order and process any returns. Your personal information is subject to the laws of the United States. The servers and databases in which information may be stored may be located outside the country from which you accessed the Services and in a country where the data protection and other laws may differ from your country of residence. Your personal information may be disclosed in response to inquiries or requests from government authorities or to respond to judicial process in the countries in which we operate.

**Q: What if I live outside of the United States?**

**A:** For residents of the European Union (and United Kingdom), Gilt is the data controller responsible for your personal information collected pursuant to this Privacy Policy. Our digital operations are conducted, in whole or in part, in the United States. Regardless of where you live, you consent to have your personal data transferred to, processed and stored in the United States, and allow Gilt to use and collect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

In addition, residents of certain countries, including European Union member states (and the United Kingdom), have some or all of the following rights with respect to personal information collected from and about them on the Services: the right to request access to, and the correction, erasure, and/or restriction of processing of, such personal information; in some instances, the right to object to the processing of such personal information; in some instances, the right to request that Gilt export, in a structured, commonly used, and machine readable format, and transmit to another controller, such personal information; and the right to withdraw, at any time, any consent to the processing of such personal information. To exercise these rights, please contact Gilt via email at [privacy@gilt.com](mailto:privacy@gilt.com).

**Q: How does Gilt communicate changes to this Policy?**

**A:** Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be noted on the home page of the Site and App with a link to the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site or App following posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept these changes. If we change the Privacy Policy in any material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you.

**Q: Who do I contact if I have additional questions or concerns about this policy?**

**A:** We welcome you to reach out if you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy practices. Please feel free to contact Gilt via email at [privacy@gilt.com](mailto:privacy@gilt.com). You also have the right to submit feedback about this Privacy Policy, or the practices described herein, to the applicable supervisory authority in your jurisdiction of residence. For all unsubscribe requests, contact [unsubscribe@gilt.com](mailto:unsubscribe@gilt.com).
